https://medomakcamp.com/privacy-policy/

Family Camp
What is Family Camp?
Family Camp
What is Family Camp?
Online Privacy Policy
When you visit the Medomak Camp and Retreat Center website your visit allows for the exchange of information. You find out about all the great things that happen every summer at Medomak. If you’re interested, it is possible for you to e-mail us, and for you to download forms to submit information to us (via U.S. Mail or fax) as you and your family prepare to join us for a wonderful family vacation.
The purpose of this document is to let you know the types of information we gather when you visit the website, and what we do with that information. This document describes how we handle the information we gather about people who visit our Web site.
Computer-based Information and Cookies
The way the Internet works allows us to capture computer-based information every time you access our website: the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com or princeton.edu); the Internet protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using when you reach our website; the browser software and operating system you are using; the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the Web site from which you directly linked to our site.
It is important to emphasize that this computer-based information is not linked to any specific user. That is, from this information it is not possible to identify you as an individual (your name) nor can any personal information be determined (address, phone, etc.).
We do collect and store computer-based information for a limited time. We use the information to analyze how our web site is used by visitors and which pages are popular. This analysis is critical for us to continue to improve our website content and “look and feel.” It should be reiterated that this type of information is not linked to any personal information. In no way does this information compromise your privacy, other than telling us that you use the Internet to find out about Medomak.
Aside from the computer-based information mentioned above, there are other ways that your accessing websites can allow companies to find out much more about you: what websites you routinely visit, how much business you do on the web and with whom. Further, once such information is known, and if it is sold or shared with others, your privacy can be compromised. To gain this additional level of information involves the exchange of “cookies.” A “cookie” is a file that a Web site can place on your computer’s hard drive in order, for example, to collect information about your activities. The cookie transmits this information back to the Web site’s computer. As with the computer-based information, people are typically unaware of the “cookies” that are being exchanged by their browser, and also unaware that certain websites use these “cookies” to allow enhanced tracking.
Medomak Camp and Retreat Center does NOT use “cookies” to track your Web surfing anywhere other than on this Web site. Using “cookies” within the Medomak website only allows the site to function more easily: “cookies” help you navigate more predictably within the site. Here again, our use of “cookies” in no way compromises your privacy.
E-mail
Should you have any reason to contact us via e-mail, we do collect personally identifying information. At the very least, we will have your name and email address. Such interactions also likely include additional personal information; address and possibly telephone number. This information is collected only to the extent you volunteer that information. We never solicit for such information.
Any personal information you offer is used strictly for internal purposes. We do not, and will not, sell or otherwise share information collected by email with other people for any commercial purposes. The only occasions upon which we would share the information would be (i) to protect the security or integrity of our website; (ii) to take precautions against liability; (iii) to respond to judicial process; or (iv) to the extent permitted under other provisions of law, to provide information to law enforcement agencies or for an investigation on a matter related to public safety.
Links From The Medomak Site to Another Website
To enhance your ability to get information about regional activities and business near Medomak Camp, we do have certain links that we offer on the Medomak Camp website. We provide such links solely as a service to visitors of the website. We do not have agreements to exchange any information between Medomak Camp and the owners of the linked sites. In short, once a visitor accesses another Web site, the visitor is subject to the privacy policy of that website.
Full Disclosure of Any Personal Information
Relative to many other camps, and many other companies, we collect very little information about anyone who visits our website. The extent of personal information we have would be as a result of receiving e-mail, or of your family having attended Medomak Camp. Regardless of how we have obtained the information, if you want to know exactly what information we have, you may contact us. We will require that you verify your identity before we will disclose any information.
Here’s How to Contact Us
Winter address:
12230 Clarksville Pike, Ste. C
Clarksville, MD 21029
Telephone:
301-854-9100
Fax:
301-854-2090
Summer address:
178 Liberty Rd
Washington, Maine 04574
Telephone:
207-845-6001
E-mail:
family@medomakcamp.com
1-866-MEDOMAK
Testimonials
Share
Participate in adult art and science retreats (or let us host yours) at our beautiful, peaceful and accommodating retreat facility just down the road.
Learn more. »
Medomak Camp is the first full-season secular family camp to be accredited by the American Camping Association.
Winter (September-May)
12230 Clarksville Pike, Suite C
Clarksville, MD 21029
(301) 854-9100
Summer (June-August)
178 Liberty Rd.
